socialsbox.com 2018-05-09

# Socialsbox.com - Buy YouTube Views | Instagram Followers | Facebook Likes | Twitter Followers

What information does SocialsBox.com collect? 

We do not require you to create an account or share any personally identifiable information in order to use our site. However, we do collect some non-personally identifiable information automatically. Further, solely at your option, you can choose to share some contact information with us. 

Information Collected Automatically We automatically collect some non-personally identifiable information about your visit, including the operating system and browser you are using, as well as the date, time, and pages you visit. Collecting this information helps us design the site to suit your needs. 

When you request a page from our site, our servers log your current IP address. An Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is a unique string of numbers that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems and to gather demographic information and measure traffic to the site. We do not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information about you. 

Information You Provide to Us (Optionally) We obtain personally identifiable information about you if you elect to send an inquiry to us through the Contact Us section of our website, or subscribe to our newsletter or marketing emails. Please note that this information is only used to communicate with you regarding your inquiry or request for a newsletter. The types of personally identifiable information we ask you to provide may include the following: 

Name  
E-mail address  
Website

Does SocialsBox.com SHARE my personally identifiable information with others? SocialsBox.com does NOT share information that we have about you with anyone. We do not share, sell, rent, or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for any reason. 

Does SocialsBox.com use COOKIES to collect information about me? A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser when you visit our site. Cookies enable our systems to recognize your computer so that we can provide you with personalized service and features, and to track traffic patterns. Although our cookies may contain a unique user ID, they do not collect or store any of your personally identifiable information. 

Also, in the course of advertising, a third party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. SocialsBox.com assumes no responsibility for any cookies placed on your browser by such third-party advertisers. 

How does SocialsBox.com SECURE the information collected? SocialsBox.com has security measures in place and takes reasonable precautions to protect against the loss, misuse, and unauthorized access of your personal information under our control. 

Does SocialsBox.com collect information from CHILDREN? At SocialsBox.com, we are committed to protecting the privacy of children. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information online from children under the age of 13. 

If you are under 13 years of age, please do not submit any personal information through our website without the express consent and participation of a parent or guardian. 

Does this policy cover OTHER sites linked from SocialsBox.com? This policy covers our online practices and does not apply to any third party sites, including card issuers or other sites that may be linked from our website. We encourage you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of those other sites to learn how they collect and use information about you.
